vivre.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy

Vivre has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting your privacy. We will not sell, rent, or distribute your name, e-mail address or other identifiable information to any third party without your consent. Please check back periodically as our privacy policy may change from time to time.   

Information Collection and Use 

To provide you the best possible products and services, we will request specific personal information when you register on vivre.com, when you make a product or gift card purchase, and when you request a catalogue. Any personal information collected on vivre is knowingly and voluntarily provided by customers and visitors to our site. 

At registration, we collect your name, shipping and billing addresses, telephone numbers, and e-mail address in order to deliver your orders promptly and to the proper location. We use your e-mail address to send you two emails following a purchase. The first confirms that your order was shipped, and provides an itemized order summary with your order number. The second e-mail provides you with a FedEx tracking number so that you can determine the status of your order. Please note that should any of your items be on-reserve, out-of-stock or discontinued, you will receive an additional email after your order confirmation specifying the specific status of each item in question. If necessary, a Customer Care Associate may contact you by telephone to resolve any issues concerning your order. 

When you make a gift card or product purchase, we collect your credit card number and your expiration date. We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We will automatically store your credit card number and expiration date on our secure server with your account so that you will not have to fill out this information again during future visits and purchases at vivre.com. This information is used solely for billing purposes when you order from vivre.com and is always encrypted and transmitted safely over the Internet using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. Please see our Security Policy for more information. 

We may occasionally run contests and other similar promotions on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (such as their e-mail address) and demographic information (such as their zip code, age, or income level). We use this contact information to send registered users and current customers and catalogue requesters information about our company as well as marketing and promotional materials from our company as well as our partners. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and your shopping cart. Your name and password are used to verify that you are a registered customer and prevent anyone else who may have access to your computer from ordering in your name without your express permission. 

Any email that you may sent to us or any correspondences are strictly confidential and are not distributed to any partner or third party. 

Any information you provide will be used to:   
1.Improve upon and personalize the Web site content and services to enhance your shopping experience;   
2.Better our customer service;   
3.Contact you about Web site updates, special offers, new products and services. 

Vivre may share non-personal, non-individual information in aggregate form with our vendors and marketing partners for research purposes. This includes aggregate data about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information. You always have the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future mailings from Vivre or our partners; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Vivre has third party relationships with credit card processing companies, shipping companies and the company from which we lease our servers. These companies only have access to information that is necessary for each to fulfill their respective roles in completing our customers' orders. 

Vivre reserves the right to share personal information with legal authorities to the extent required by law. 

Information Collection and Use

To provide you the best possible products and services, we will request specific personal information when you register on vivre.com, when you make a product or gift card purchase, and when you request a catalogue. Any personal information collected on vivre is knowingly and voluntarily provided by customers and visitors to our site. 

At registration, we collect your name, shipping and billing addresses, telephone numbers, and e-mail address in order to deliver your orders promptly and to the proper location. We use your e-mail address to send you two emails following a purchase. The first confirms that your order was shipped, and provides an itemized order summary with your order number. The second e-mail provides you with a FedEx tracking number so that you can determine the status of your order. Please note that should any of your items be on-reserve, out-of-stock or discontinued, you will receive an additional email after your order confirmation specifying the specific status of each item in question. If necessary, a Customer Care Associate may contact you by telephone to resolve any issues concerning your order. 

When you make a gift card or product purchase, we collect your credit card number and your expiration date. We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We will automatically store your credit card number and expiration date on our secure server with your account so that you will not have to fill out this information again during future visits and purchases at vivre.com. This information is used solely for billing purposes when you order from vivre.com and is always encrypted and transmitted safely over the Internet using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. Please see our Security Policy for more information. 

We may occasionally run contests and other similar promotions on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (such as their e-mail address) and demographic information (such as their zip code, age, or income level). We use this contact information to send registered users and current customers and catalogue requesters information about our company as well as marketing and promotional materials from our company as well as our partners. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and your shopping cart. Your name and password are used to verify that you are a registered customer and prevent anyone else who may have access to your computer from ordering in your name without your express permission. 

Any email that you may sent to us or any correspondences are strictly confidential and are not distributed to any partner or third party. 

Any information you provide will be used to:   
1.Improve upon and personalize the Web site content and services to enhance your shopping experience;   
2.Better our customer service;   
3.Contact you about Web site updates, special offers, new products and services. 

Vivre may share non-personal, non-individual information in aggregate form with our vendors and marketing partners for research purposes. This includes aggregate data about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information. You always have the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future mailings from Vivre or our partners; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Vivre has third party relationships with credit card processing companies, shipping companies and the company from which we lease our servers. These companies only have access to information that is necessary for each to fulfill their respective roles in completing our customers' orders. 

Vivre reserves the right to share personal information with legal authorities to the extent required by law. 

Notification of Changes in the Use of Your Personal Information

Should any changes occur in our use of your personal information, you will be notified by email prior to the changes. You will always have the opportunity to opt-out prior to the implementation of such changes. 

Co-branded Relationships

vivre.com has developed strategic partnerships in which users may experience vivre.com within a co-branded environment alongside one of our partners. Co-branded pages are recognizable usually by the presence of a "frame" either at the top or bottom of the page and/or when both companies' brand logos are presented together on the page. In such situations, individual user information may be shared only between our two companies in an effort to better understand and meet our customers' needs. Should you have additional privacy concerns, please also refer to the privacy policy of our partner from whose site you visited prior to arriving at vivre.com. 

Cookies

Vivre uses a feature of your Internet browser called a "cookie" to assign a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are files that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive. Vivre creates and then uses these cookie files to track your clicks as you browse the Vivre Web site. 

Vivre uses cookies to tell us whether you have visited Vivre previously and to help us determine whether you came to Vivre from a particular Internet link or banner advertisement. 

Cookies can also be used to help save and retrieve user names and passwords used on our site and information on past purchases and personal preferences. Should you disable the use of cookies on your browser, you will need to re-enter this information whenever you visit our site. Vivre will not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer unless you specifically and willingly provide this information. 

Choice/Opt-Out

Vivre provides customers the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the customer. We give you the following options to change or modify your information in our database and to choose not to receive future communications. 

You can visit our email opt-out form by clicking here  
You can send email to [customercare@vivre.com](mailto:customercare@vivre.com)  
You can visit the My Account page (sign-in required)  
You can call the following telephone number: 800.411.6515 

Security

Shopping and buying online with your credit card is actually statistically more secure than using it in a department store. And, at Vivre, our customers' privacy and security are a top priority. We take every precaution to protect your online order information. 

Our checkout and confirmation areas are secured using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. SSL technology ensures that your credit card number and personal data are never sent over the Internet unencrypted. Once we receive your credit card information, it is immediately and securely stored in its encrypted form in our data center. Once it is encrypted, only the credit card authorization company can decrypt it. Your credit card number is never displayed on our site—only the first and last four digits will ever be shown. Even our Customer Care associates only have access to your card's first digit, last four digits, and expiration date. 

You can have full confidence in the security of your transactions while shopping with Vivre. However, should you prefer to order by telephone, we are happy to take your order at 800.411.6515.
